Finding Aid for the Ernest Fleischmann Papers LSC.2293
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2: Los Angeles Philharmonic, 1970-2010
  - Subseries 2.2: Correspondence and subject files, 1980-2008
    - The Orchestra Leadership Academy, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Orchestral Repertoire Timings: Henry Fogel Record Library, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 2-3)
    - Organizations, 1982-1985 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Paris Opera, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Paris Opera: Convention Collectives, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 1-3, Box 6, Folder 15-16)
    - Paris Opera: correspondence to M. Angremy, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Paris Opera: orchestra and building plans, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Paris Opera: Paris trip, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 14-15)
    - Paris Opera: resignation, 1985 November-1985 December (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Philadelphia Symphony Orchestra, 2003-2005 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Philharmonic Society of Orange County, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Previn, Andre, 1987-1989 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Rachmaninoff Piano Competition, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Rattle, Simon, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Rundfunk Orchester und Chöre Berlin, 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Salonen, Esa-Pekka: final program, 2008-2009 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Salonen, Esa-Pekka: correspondence, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Salonen, Esa-Pekka: clippings, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Salzburg Festival, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Salzburg Festival: Symposia, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Salzburg Seminars, 2000-2003 (Box 18, Folder 2-5)
    - San Francisco Ballet, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - San Francisco Ballet: candidates, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - San Francisco Symphony, 1998-2002 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - San Jose Symphony, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Sapporo Concert Hall, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Schleswig-Holstein festival and chorus, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Seattle Symphony, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - South Africa, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - South West Chamber Music, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Spoleto Orizzonte, 1998-2005 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - St. Petersburg Philharmonic, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Sydney International Piano, 2000-2004 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Teatro Lirico Sperimentale, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Theatre National Opera de Paris, 1983-1986 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Trade agreements, 1989-1992 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Unisa International Piano Competition, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - USC, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - USC Thornton School of Music, 2004-2007 (Box 20, Folder 8-9)
    - Venezuela: La Sistema, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Weingarten, Elmar: Berliner Philharmonisches, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - White Nights Foundation, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Wijbergen, Willem, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - William Kraft Foundation, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Winnipeg Symphony Orchestra, 2003-2008 (Box 18, Folder 9, Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Witt, Karsten, 2007-2008 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Youth Orchestra, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 2.3: Programs and publicity materials, 1970-2010
    Subseries contains newspaper clippings, magazine articles, and other press related to the LA Phil and Fleischmann. Also includes a significant amount of programs and program books, both from the LA Phil and orchestras and venues around the world.
    - Access badges/cards, 1994-1996 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Announcement of retirement, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Article re Frank Gehry & The Walt Disney Concert from "Archithese", 1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Articles, 2006 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      Includes articles printed off of the internet as well as assorted brochures and correspondence.
    - Arts magazines, 1987-1997 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Assorted clippings and concert schedules, 1987-2000 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Classical programs and notes, 1973-2010 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1997-2007 (Box 26, Folder 10, Box 92, Folder 8, Box 65, Folder 3-4)
    - Clippings: Hollywood Bowl, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Clippings: Hollywood Bowl, Zubin Mehta, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Clippings: Classical music (photocopies), 1941 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Clippings: "Is Music Safe From Dissonance?", 1992 May 22 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Clippings: Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Commendation by Mayor Bradley, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Distinguished Artist Award Gala, 2001 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - "International Arts Manager", 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Los Angeles Times Calendar: "The Grand Finale", 1998 February 15 (Box 15, Folder 4, Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Los Angeles Times Magazine: "The Importance of Being Ernest", 1989 October 8 (Box 15, Folder 2-3, Box 10, Folder 3)
    - New York Times Magazine: "The Importance of Being Fleischmann", 1976 April 11 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Orchestras in magazines, 1986-2008 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Press release: Andre Previn, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Program books, 1980s-2000s (Box 93, Folder 10, Box 97, Folder 1-5, Box 96, Box 95, Box 94, Folder 2-5)
    - Programs, clippings, and conference proceedings, 1960s-2010 (Box 92, Folder 7, Box 94, Folder 1, Box 65, Folder 1,5, Box 66, Folder 1,3,6-7, Box 22, Folder 14, Box 64, Folder 3, Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Programs, concert schedules, and brochures, 1990s-2010 (Box 61, Box 62, Box 63, Box 64, Folder 1-2, 4)
    - Programs: Chatelet, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Programs: Entartete Musik, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Programs: Gustavo Dudamel, 2009 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Programs: Hollywood Bowl, 1924-1997 (Box 5, Folder 10, Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Programs: LAPO, 1996-1999 (Box 14, Folder 7, Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Rudolf Serkin feature, undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Walt Disney Concert Hall, 1988-1995 May (Box 9, Folder 3-4, Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Winter Season 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Winter Season 1999-2000, 1998-2000 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Series 3: Fleischmann Arts, 1992-2010
  Contains an assortment of material related to Fleischmann's many consultancies under the auspices of Fleishmann Arts, his arts consulting organization. Among the many organizations Fleishmann worked with, a great deal of material pertains to the Colburn Foundation, where he often served as a consultant to the Board of Directors. Also included in this series are materials related to Fleischmann's tenure as Artistic Director of the Ojai Festival (1998-2003) and Program Director for the American Friends of the Salzburg Festival. The series includes correspondence, meeting minutes, programs, memoranda, and a small amount of financial material.
  - Subseries 3.1: Consultancies and administrative files, 1992-2008
    Contains administrative files and correspondence related to the numerous musicians and arts organizations for which Fleischmann served as a consultant, artistic advisor, and featured speaker, both in the United States and Europe. Also includes a large amount of material related to the Salzburg Festival, a prominent Austrian summer music festival, as well as materials pertaining to his role as juror in world-wide musical competitions, including the Gustav Mahler Conducting Competition which launched Gustavo Dudamel's career in 2004.
    - Adams, John, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Adelaide Symphony Orchestra, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - American Youth Symphony, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Artists, 1998-2004 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Artists' Fees, 1992-1994 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Artists' Fees, 1994-1995 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Artists' Fees, 1995-1998 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Artists' Managers, undated (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - ASOL, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Association of California Symphony Orchestras, 2010 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Association of French Orchestras, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Avery Fisher Artist Program, 1998-2000 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Bamberger Symphoniker, 2006-2007 (Box 44, Folder 3-4)
    - Berio, Luciano, 1998-2002 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Berlin Symphonie-Orchester, 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Bilbao, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Bonn Concert Hall, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Boosey and Hawkes, Inc., 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Boulez, Pierre, 2000-2005 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Boulez, Pierre, 1992-1998 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Brady, William H., III, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Bringuier documentary, 2000s (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Bringuier, Lionel, 2006-2007 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Brochures: A, 2005-2008 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Brochures: Ba-Be, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Brochures: Be-Ci, 2005-2006 (Box 43, Folder 3-5)
    - Brochures: Co-F, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Brochures: G-H, 2005-2009 (Box 67, Folder 1-2)
    - Brochures: I-K, 2005-2009 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Brochures: L.A. Opera, 2005-2009 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Brochures: Los Angeles Orchestras, 2007-2008 (Box 67, Folder 5-6)
    - Bruno Walter Foundation: Joachim Streseman, 1998-2000 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Cal Arts, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Camerata Pacifica, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Cape Town Philharmonic Orchestra, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Carnegie Hall: Ohnesorg, Guzelimian, 1998-2003 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Center for Jazz Arts, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Chisholm, Erik, 2000s (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Chronological files, 1998-2001 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Chronological files, 1998-2001 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Chronological files, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 1-4)
    - Chronological files, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 14-16, Box 49, Folder 1-5)
    - Chronological files, 2000-2001 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Chronological files, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 1-3)
    - Chronological files, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Chronological files, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Chronological files, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Chronological files, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Chronological files, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Client fees, 1999 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, 2004 August 24 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Conductor evaluations, 1992 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Conductors to watch: A-M, 1997-2004 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Conductors to watch: N-Z, 1998-2002 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Conductors to watch: random lists, formal searches, 1998-2006 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Consultancies correspondence, 1998-2006 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Consultancies: U, 1999-2001 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Consultancies: V, 1998-2000 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Consultancies: W, 1999-2000 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1998-2002 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (fax), 2001 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, news release: Gold Baton Award, Fleischmann Arts, Ojai Festival, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Donations, 1997-2006 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Dudamel, Gustavo, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - EF and Pierre Boulez, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Fax activity reports, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Fax Correspondence, 2001 January-2001 March (Box 40, Folder 13-14)
    - Faxes, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 1-5)
    - Fictitious Name Registration, 1998-2000 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Finnish Consulate, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Fleischmann biographies, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Fort Worth Symphony Music Director Search, 1998-2000 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
    - General correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Getty Center, 1998-2002 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Gueller, Bernhard, 1999-2004 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Harrison/Parrott Ltd., 2001 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Hollywood Bowl, 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
    - ICM Artists, 1998-2000 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - "I" correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - International Alliance of Orchestra Associations, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - International Stiftung Mozarteum, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Japan, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - "J" correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Joyce Ketay Agency, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - "K" correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Kent, Louis, 1997-2000 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Kigawa, Taka, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - KKGO, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 13, Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Kreizberg, Yakov, 1997-2000 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Kyoto Concert Hall, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - "L" correspondence, 1998-2002 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Lee, Norman, 1998-2000 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Leon Botstein, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Logo, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - London Philharmonic Orchestra, 1995-2000 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Los Angeles Children's Chorus, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Los Angeles Times article, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Lucerne Festival, 2002-2004 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Mahler bust: Marina Mahler, 1997-2004 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Mahler Conducting Competition, 2001-2004 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Mahler Conducting Competition, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Mahler, Marine, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Mahler, Marina, 1998-1999 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Majer, Karl-Ulrich, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Manzanar, 2001-2002 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Manzanar project, 2002-2003 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Mariinsky Theater, 2001-2002 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Mattner, Lothar ASOL/ASPEN, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Meet the Composer, 1998-2000 (Box 55, Folder 3-4)
    - Memphis Symphony Orchestra search, 2008 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Monday Evening Concerts, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Monte Carlo Masters, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Monte Carlo Music Masters piano competition, 2000-2007 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Musica Noval Festival: Helskinki, 2002-2003 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Nagata Acoustics, 1998-2002 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - NDR, 1997-1999 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - NDR Sinfonieorchester, 2001 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - NDRSO U.S. Tour, 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 4-6)
    - New York City Ballet, 1998-1999 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - New York City Ballet, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - New Musk Summit/Biennale/Worldfest, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Notes and ephemera, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Ohyama, Heiichiro, 2001-2003 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Opera Administrators, 2001 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Opera miscellaneous, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Orchester de Bretagne, 2003-2005 (Box 44, Folder 7-8)
    - Paris Conference, circa 2001-2003 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - "P" Correspondence, 1998-2002 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Phone log, 1999-2001 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Rattle, Simon, 1999-2001 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - RAU Cultural Office, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - "R" correspondence, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Resumes, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Royal Philharmonic Society, 1999-2001 (Box 36, Folder 8-9)
    - Salonen, Esa-Pekka, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Salzburg Festival, 1999-2005 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Salzburg Festival, 2000-2001 (Box 52, Folder 15, Box 47, Folder 2-3)
    - Salzburg Festival: Programs, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Salzburg Seminar, 2002-2003 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Salzburg Seminar: "The Recess, Cultural Change and a Glut of Orchestras", 1993 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco Opera, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Schleswig-Holstein Music Festival, 1988-1999 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Schleswig-Holstein Music Festival, 1998-2005 (Box 60, Folder 16, Box 55, Folder 10-11)
    - "S" Correspondence, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Seventh Regiment Armory Conservancy, 2000-2001 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Spoleto, 1997-1998 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Suleiman, Alexander- Cellist, 2004-2006 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Sundays Live, 2006 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Sydney International Piano Competition, 1995-1999 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Taormina Festival, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - "T" Correspondence, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Temirkanov, Yuri, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - The Ten, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Tickets, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Toradze Institute, Indiana University, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Travel, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Travel, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - UCLA, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - USC Thornton School of Music board information, undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Van Walsum Management, 2001-2002 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Villa Aurora, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Westdeutscher Rundfunk Köln, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Who's Who in Music, 1998-2000 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Witt, Karsten Musik Management, 2007 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Worby, Rachael, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - World music, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Yelda, Guy, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 3.2: Ojai Festival, 1996-2007
    Includes administrative records, board minutes, funding documentation, correspondence, and programs and books related to the Ojai Music Festival, a classical music festival held annually in Ojai, California, for which Fleischmann served as Artistic Director from 1998-2003.
    - Architectural plans: Libby Bowl Amphitheater, 1999 (Box 100)
    - Artists and programs, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Artists, contracts, accommodations, 1999-2000 (Box 39, Folder 1-3)
    - Board meetings, 1997-1998 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors and budget, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Books, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Books, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Brochures, programs, flyers, newsletters, 2000 May-2000 June (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Brochures: Lucerne, 2005-2009 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: resignation, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Pierre Boulez and Lawrence Morton, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Creative Music Award, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Development, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Development, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Development, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Director's letters, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Finnish Arts Program, 1998-1999 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Fundraising, 1997-1998 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Grants, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Grants, 1998-1999 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Invitation, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - LAPA and Ojai Festivals, 1998-2008 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Libbey Bowl Shell, 1999-2000 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Musicales, 1998-1999 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Music/Education Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Music education, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Ojai Festival, 1996-1997 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Ojai Festival, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Ojai Festival, 1997-1998 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Ojai Festival, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Ojai Festival, 1998-2001 (Box 53, Folder 1-3)
    - Ojai Festival, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Ojai Festival, 2000-2001 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Ojai Festival, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Ojai Festival, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Ojai Festival, 2002-2007 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Ojai Festival, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Operating budget, 1998-1999 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Operating budget, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Press, 1999 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Program books, 1986-1996 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Programs, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Programs, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Program notes and copy, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Programs, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Program notes and copy, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Programs, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Programs, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Publicity and promotion, 1998-1999 (Box 54, Folder 6-7)
    - Publicity and promotion, 2000 May-2000 June (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Publicity, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Sponsors and fundraising, 1998-1999 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Sponsors, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Symposium, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Symposium, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Ticket prices, 1999-2000 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Tickets, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 3.3: Colburn Foundation, 1998-2010
    Contains board and program committee minutes for the Colburn Foundation, a nonprofit established in 1999 and endowed by Richard D. Colburn, with a mission of promoting classical music in Southern California through grants. Included are materials pertaining to Musica Angelica, a program funded by the Colburn Foundation.
    - Agreement, 2000-2010 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Board meeting, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Board meetings, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Board meeting, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Board meeting, 2005 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Board meetings, 2006 (Box 72, Folder 4-5)
    - Board meetings, 2008 (Box 71, Folder 1-3)
    - Board meeting, 2009 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Board meeting, 2009 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Board meeting, 2009 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Board meeting, 2009 April (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Board meetings, 2010 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Board meetings, 2010 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Board meeting, 2010 April (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Board of Visitors Handbook, 2006 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Colburn School of Music, 1998-2001 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Colburn School of Music, 1999-2001 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Colburn School of Music, 2002-2004 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Colburn School: Board of Visitors, 2006 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Colburn School: Conductor Training Program, 2007 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Consultations, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Contacts, 1999-2005 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Financial statements, 2009-2010 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Long Beach Opera, 2009 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Memorandum, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Memorandum, 2009 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Musica Angelica, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Musica Angelica, 2001-2002 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Musica Angelica, 2003-2004 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Musica Angelica, 2003-2008 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Musica Angelica, 2004-2005 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Musica Angelica, 2006-2007 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Musica Angelica, 2006-2008 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Musica Angelica: 2007-2008 Season (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Musica Angelica: 2008-2009 Season (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Musica Angelica, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Musica Angelica: Finance Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Musica Angelica: reports and memos, 2005-2006 (Box 70, Folder 2-3)
    - Musica Angelica: reports and memos, 2007 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Musica Angelica: reports, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Oral History: Richard D. Colburn, 2004 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Philharmonic and Colburn galas, 1998-2006 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Program Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Program Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Program Committee and consulting, 2006-2007 (Box 70, Folder 4-5)
    - Program Committee, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Program Committee meeting, 2009 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Program Committee meeting, 2009 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Program Committee meeting, 2010 April (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Termination of Rae Kate Shen, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Young Musicians Foundation, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Series 4: Writings and personal materials, 1960-2010
  Series contains materials of a personal nature, including personal correspondence, awards and plaques, collected historical newspaper clippings, and photographs. Also inlcuded are originals and copies of Fleischmann's writings including speeches, articles, and manuscripts as well as notes for a memoir.
  - Articles and press releases, 1976-1997 (Box 93, Folder 6, Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Assorted writings, undated (Box 93, Folder 4-5)
  - Awards and plaques (Box 98)
  - "BALLADE" publication, 1989 November 3 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Banner, circa 1990s (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Boulez, Pierre, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 8)